goodprint.co.uk 2013-11-24

# Privacy policy

By using the Goodprint site you consent to our cookie policy

### 1\. ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY

    This acceptable use policy sets out the terms between you and us under which you may access our Site. This document together with the documents referred to on it tells you the terms of use on which you may make use of our Site whether as a guest or a registered user. Please read these terms of use carefully before you start to use the site.
    Your use of our Site means that you accept, and agree to abide by, all the policies in this acceptable use policy. If you do not agree to these terms of use or to any of the terms and conditions on which we supply any of the products listed on our Site, please refrain from using our Site.
1.1 Prohibited Uses
     You may use our Site only for lawful purposes. You may not use our Site: 

    a) In any way that breaches any applicable local, national or international law or regulation.
    b) In any way that is unlawful or fraudulent, or has any unlawful or fraudulent purpose or effect.
    c) For the purpose of harming or attempting to harm minors in any way.
    d) To upload any material which does not comply with our content standards.
    e) To knowingly transmit any data or upload any material that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time-bombs, keystroke loggers, spyware, adware or any other harmful programs or similar computer code designed to adversely affect the operation of any computer software or hardware.
     You also agree: 

    a) Not to reproduce, duplicate, copy or re-sell any part of our Site.
    b) Not to access without authority, interfere with, damage or disrupt:

    any part of our Site;
    any equipment or network on which our Site is stored; 
    any software used in the provision of our Site; or
    any equipment or network or software owned or used by any third party.
1.2 Content standards
    These content standards apply to any and all material which you upload onto our Site ("Uploads").
    You must comply with the spirit of the following standards. The standards apply to each part of any contribution as well as to its whole.
    **Contributions must** :

    a) Be accurate.
    b) Comply with applicable law in the UK and in any country from which they are uploaded.
    **Contributions must not:**

    a) Contain any material which is defamatory of any person.
    b) Contain any material which is obscene, offensive, hateful or inflammatory.
    c) Promote sexually explicit material.
    d) Promote violence.
    e) Promote discrimination based on race, sex, religion, nationality, disability, sexual orientation or age.
    f) Infringe any copyright, database right or trade mark of any other person.
    g) Be likely to deceive any person.
    h) Be made in breach of any legal duty owed to a third party, such as a contractual duty or a duty of confidence.
    i) Promote any illegal activity.
    j) Be threatening, abuse or invade another's privacy, or cause annoyance, inconvenience or needless anxiety.
    k) Be likely to harass, upset, embarrass alarm or annoy any other person.
    l) Be used to impersonate any person, or to misrepresent your identity or affiliation with any person.
    m) Give the impression that they emanate from us, if this is not the case.
    n) Advocate, promote or assist any unlawful act such as (by way of example only) copyright infringement or computer misuse.
1.3 Suspension and termination
    We will determine, in our discretion, whether there has been a breach of this acceptable use policy through your use of our Site. When a breach of this policy has occurred, we may take such action as we deem appropriate.
    Failure to comply with this acceptable use policy constitutes a material breach of the terms and conditions which can be accessed through a link on our homepage at http://www.goodprint.co.uk.
    It may result in our taking all or any of the following actions:

    a) Immediate, temporary or permanent withdrawal of your right to use our Site.
    b) Immediate, temporary or permanent removal of any material uploaded by you to our Site.
    c) Issue of a warning to you.
    d) Legal proceedings against you for reimbursement of all costs on an indemnity basis (including, but not limited to, reasonable administrative and legal costs) resulting from the breach.
    e) Further legal action against you.
    f) Disclosure of such information to law enforcement authorities as we reasonably feel is necessary.
    We exclude liability for actions taken in response to breaches of this acceptable use policy. The responses described in this policy are not limited, and we may take any other action we reasonably deem appropriate.
1.4 Changes to the acceptable use policy
    We may revise this acceptable use policy at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we make, as they are legally binding on you. Some of the provisions contained in this acceptable use policy may also be superseded by provisions or notices published elsewhere on our Site.

### 2\. PRIVACY POLICY

    In general, we use the information we collect about you to:

    a) help our members provide more personalised services to you.
    b) provide information to relevant third parties.
    c) improve the features and services we offer.
    d) support our own marketing and promotion efforts.
2.1 Information we collect from you
    We may collect and process the following data about you:

    a) Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Site. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services . We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by us and when you report a problem with our Site.
    b) If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
    c) We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
    d) Details of transactions you carry out through our Site and of the fulfilment of your orders.
    e) Details of your visits to our Site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.
    f) Information about your identity (which may also be disclosed to any third party who is claiming that any material uploaded by you to our Site constitutes a violation of their rights).
2.2 Where we store your personal data
    All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
    Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
2.3 Uses made of the information
    We use information held about you in the following ways:

    a) To ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
    b) To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
    c) To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
    d) To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
    e) To notify you about changes to our service.
    We may also use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post, email or telephone.
    If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the [order form OR registration form]).
2.4 Your Rights
    You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us.
    our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
2.5 Our right to extend these policies
    The right to use the terms within this policy (in relation to any information that you upload) and those contained within the Terms and Conditions [link to Terms and Conditions] extend to anyone who succeeds ownership of our business. They have the right to use such information for the purpose of carrying out the service they provide in conjunction with the service we provide.
2.6 Access to information
    The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £50.00 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
2.7 Changes to our Privacy Policy
    Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

### 3\. COOKIE POLICY

    We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users\' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
    For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer\'s hard drive. They help us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

    a) To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
    b) To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our Site according to your individual interests.
    c) To speed up your searches.
    d) To recognise you when you return to our Site.
    You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Site.

### Contact

    Questions, comments and requests regarding any of the policies above are welcomed, and should be addressed to Graham Orr at 84-86 Great Portland, Street London, W1W 7NR.
